{
    "subject": "resource/Urapopstar",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Game",
    "human_readable": "Urapopstar is a game.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9678143262863159,
            "question": "Is Urapopstar a popular game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8650097846984863,
            "question": "Can you play Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8414090275764465,
            "question": "Who created the game Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855768799781799,
            "question": "What are the main gameplay mechanics of Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.779140055179596,
            "question": "What type of thing is Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7011040449142456,
            "question": "What makes Urapopstar unique compared to other games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6639725565910339,
            "question": "What platforms is Urapopstar available on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6432368755340576,
            "question": "Are there any characters in Urapopstar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5673688054084778,
            "question": "Does Urapopstar have a story mode?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4060395359992981,
            "question": "Has Urapopstar won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Urapopstar is a game.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9068_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Urapopstar have a story mode?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9068_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any characters in Urapopstar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9068_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What platforms is Urapopstar available on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9068_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9068_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Urapopstar is described as a multiplayer browser-based role-playing game, which confirms that it is indeed a game."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}